MUKESH MISHRA

SAP FICO CONSULTANT

+91 8928810890 mmukesh914@gmail.com in LinkedIn 2 Navi Mumbai

PROFILE

SAP FICO Consultant with over 1.7 years of experience providing live support to various client with different line of business.

Having expertise with more than 5 + years of experience in Accounts and Finance which guide me to understand the requirement of the client in a better way for providing better solution for smooth business process.

SAP SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Configuration of Enterprise Structure, Financial Accounting & Controlling.
- Configuration of General ledger, Maintaining masters and Accounting.
- Configuration of A/R & A/P, Maintaining Masters, and Accounting.
- Configuration of Validation and Substitution.
- Configuration of Indirect Taxes
- Configuration of Bank Accounts
- Development and Change request of Various reports: Procure to Pay report(P2P), GSTR-2 Report, Customer Statement of Accounts Report, cheque bounce report and Mail trigger, Upload program through BAPI.
- Also familiar with Asset Accounting, Profit Center & Cost center Configuration & Accounting.

EXPERIENCE

April 2022 – till date	FICO Consultant Ernst & Young LLP. 1.7 + Years of experience as SAP FICO Consultant in Ernst &
	Young LLP. till Present which includes 9 Month prior experience in Eborn Consulting Pvt. Ltd. (EY Subsidiary)
June 2018 – Mar 2022	Accounts & Finance Executive Eborn Consulting Pvt. Ltd. (EY Subsidiary)
	Maintaining Accounts of Books, General Ledger Accounting, Accounts Payable & Receivable, Vendor and Customer Ageing Reports, Bank Reconciliation and Auditing, Helping in Finalizing Profit & Loss, and Balance sheet.
Dec 2016 – April 2018	Accounts & Finance & Audit Executive CA V.V Rane & Company.
	GST Returns filing, Auditing and Income Tax return filings, Helping in Finalizing Profit & Loss, and Balance sheet.

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Support to the existing SAP in the areas of GL, AP, AR, MM & SD integration with FI.
- Coordinating the team for timely deliverables.
- Involvement in Development, Configuration, and Support of FICO Module.
- Participated in requirement gathering & preparing functional specifications reports.
- Gathering the information based on the identified custom processes & Interfaces based on the customer requirement document relating to FI functionalities.
- Involved in configuration of accounts payable and related open item management for the client.
- Regularly interacted with the users to ensure proper understanding of the business requirements and functional specifications.
- Preparing the Configuration Documents, Test cases and design function specification documents.
- Specified testing requirements, planned tests, executed tests, and tracked defects with Quality center.
- Responsible for user acceptance (UAT) of custom ABAP Program from the functional point of view.

PRODUCTS

SAP S4 HANA & SAP ECC 6.0 EHP-8

INDUSTRY'S WORKED FOR

- SERVICE SECTOR INDUSTRY
- MANUFACTURING INDUSTRY
- PHARMA INDUSTRY

- AUTOMOTIVE INDUSTRY
- AGRICULTURE INDUSTRY
- HEALTH CARE INDUSTRY

EDUCATION

Nov 2021	Master's in commerce Mumbai University
	Completed my masters in Nov 2021 and was placed in 2 nd class with the
	Overall, 53.62%
Mar 2016	Bachelor's in commerce
	Mumbai University
	Completed my bachelor's in April 2016 and was placed in B Grade with
	Overall, 63%